Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
"Tide of Love"
(Episode 1)
The professor said this
when he explained perspective.
The bigger the comparison object is,
the smaller a person looks.
Right now.
I'm the ant inside that picture.
Mom.
I got a part-time job.
I'm so embarrassed I can't even lift my head.
What kind of job it is.
More specifically
I just can't bring myself to tell you.
But.
With the money it pays,
I can finally cover
your hospital bills.
If you can just get healthy again,
I don't really care
about my pride.
Even though I'm still young,
but now,
I've toughened up a little.
If your surgery goes well.
I can endure anything.
I can
do anything.
Hello.
The tenth one.
Give me the suitcase.
It's okay.
I'll do it.
Not even a hello.
Not a single word.
Feels like I'm some kind of product.
You're the tenth art-student pick
my secretary selected for me.
I only sleep with art students.
I have three rules.
First.
Come whenever I call.
Second.
Keep your distance from everyone except me.
Third.
Absolute
obedience.
Stay away from everyone.
Even my professors.
Even my friends.
Even my creative world.
And my Monday class?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Understood, sir.
What's this wound?
Does it hurt?
It's fine
right now.
If you break my rules,
I can make you hurt more than this.
Do you understand?
Let's stop.
So you tend to lose control, too...
Come in.
I left the contract time and amount blank.
You decide.
The higher the amount,
the more you can handle.
Mom's surgery fees.
Tuition.
Endure it.
Once this night is over,
maybe everything will change.
Han Jae-hoon.
He's just the first party on the contract.
All of this
is just work to me.
Then.
One night.
And one thousand dollars.
Do I look pitiful to you?
Alright.
But.
Two thousand dollars?
It might hurt even more.
Will you be okay?
Ouch!
What was that expression just now?
If you don't like it
you can say so now.
No.
It's okay.
Relax.
From now on,
everything will feel familiar.
Your kissing skills are
better than I thought.
More impressive than I expected.
From now on, your time
your body
and sometimes even your heart
all of it belongs to me.
You're crazy.
Sir.
Yeah.
I'm crazy.
Look closely.
This is what you wanted.
"Tide of Love"